<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="7350" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-13T15:54:16.460" Score="0" ViewCount="39" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want a read DjVu files on my kindle. I don't want to convert DjVu to PDF or MOBI. Is there a way I can do that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9889" LastEditorUserId="9889" LastEditDate="2017-08-14T02:07:58.147" LastActivityDate="2017-08-14T02:07:58.147" Title="How to read DjVu files on Kindle?" Tags="&lt;kindle&gt;&lt;ebook-readers&gt;&lt;kindle-paperwhite&gt;&lt;djvu&gt;&lt;apps&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7351" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7359" CreationDate="2017-08-14T07:11:33.563" Score="0" ViewCount="22" Body="&lt;p&gt;is there any way to browse available Adobe Digital Editions books? I would like to download some but do not exactly know what I am looking for and some sort of a library would be good. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9893" LastEditorUserId="60" LastEditDate="2017-08-14T16:26:27.063" LastActivityDate="2017-08-16T18:44:03.420" Title="Find new books in Adobe Digital Edition - library" Tags="&lt;adobe-digital-editions&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7352" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7351" CreationDate="2017-08-14T10:05:50.993" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Many distributors use Adobe DRM to secure their books. Some of the best known include:  B&amp;amp;N, Sony, Kobo, and Overdrive. But all have their own branded reading system that the user uses for opening these files. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Typically, some books use encryption (known as DRM) to protect its books. Adobe DE allows the reader to view ebooks with DRM if the publisher or distributor includes this particular DRM. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As it happens, many distributors, rather than sell you this DRMed file, just build their own reading system which incorporates in some way Adobe DE.  Typically it does not make sense for publishers to sell you an encrypted file because they expect you to read it in a special app (like Overdrive, Nook, Kobo, etc). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The reason publishers don't typically do this is that they  would need to purchase a special server to distribute Adobe DE files. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.adobe.com/solutions/ebook/digital-editions/faq.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;From the FAQ:&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Adobe offers a content protection service, Adobe Content Server. Adobe&#xA;  Content Server is a robust server solution that digitally protects PDF&#xA;  and reflowable EPUB content for Adobe Digital Editions and supported&#xA;  mobile devices. Easy to integrate into existing systems using industry&#xA;  standard technologies, Content Server allows you to host, manage, and&#xA;  deliver files from your existing infrastructure to Digital Editions&#xA;  users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Truthfully, publishers would prefer to work through a distributor's reading app than encrypt the file themselves and sell it directly to the consumer. It can be somewhat confusing for users to open and read stuff in Adobe DE. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adobe DE can also read unencrypted PDFs and epub files, and that is the primary way people use it. I'm a publisher, and I find it useful for testing ebook files that I create. Occasionally a publisher will send a file which can only be readable in an app which accepts Adobe DRM, but that is only if the publisher runs the Adobe Content server. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="417" LastActivityDate="2017-08-14T10:05:50.993" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7353" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6801" CreationDate="2017-08-14T14:24:40.490" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Sumatra will run under Windows 10, is very lightweight and can support both epub and pdf files. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2780" LastActivityDate="2017-08-14T14:24:40.490" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7355" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7287" CreationDate="2017-08-14T17:55:40.660" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Add this css to Indesign (this should be a text file but I'm not going to go through it and add four spaces to each line)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;/*&#xA;This document has been created with Marked.app &lt;a href=&quot;http://markedapp.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://markedapp.com&lt;/a&gt;, Copyright 2011 Brett Terpstra&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Please leave this notice in place, along with any additional credits below.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Title:  Manuscript&#xA;Author:  Brett Terpstra&#xA;Description:  Courier, Double-spaced&#xA;*/&#xA;body {&#xA;  -webkit-font-smoothing: subpixel-antialiased;&#xA;  font: normal 1em/2.5em &quot;Courier&quot;, monospace;&#xA;  margin: 4em 1in 1in 4em;&#xA;  width: auto; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;html &gt; body {&#xA;  font-size: 12pt; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h1 {&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  font-size: 2.2857em;&#xA;  margin: .6563em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h2 {&#xA;  font-size: 1.7143em;&#xA;  margin: .875em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h3 {&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  font-size: 1.5em;&#xA;  margin: 1em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h4 {&#xA;  font-size: 1.2857em;&#xA;  margin: 1.1667em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h5 {&#xA;  font-size: 1.15em;&#xA;  margin: 1.3em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h6 {&#xA;  font-size: 1em;&#xA;  margin: 1.5em 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;body, p, td, div {&#xA;  color: #111111;&#xA;  font-family: &quot;Courier&quot;, monospace;&#xA;  word-wrap: break-word; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h1, h2, h3, h4, h5, h6 {&#xA;  color: #111111;&#xA;  font-family: &quot;Helvetica Neue&quot;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;&#xA;  line-height: 1.5em; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;a {&#xA;  color: #0d6ea1;&#xA;  text-decoration: none;&#xA;  -webkit-transition: color 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -moz-transition: color 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -o-transition: color 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -ms-transition: color 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  transition: color 0.2s ease-in-out; }&#xA;  a:hover {&#xA;    color: #3593d9; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;.footnote {&#xA;  color: #0d6ea1;&#xA;  font-size: .8em;&#xA;  vertical-align: super; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1&gt;wrapper img {&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;max-width: 100%;&#xA;  height: auto; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dd {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 1em; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;li &gt; p:first-child {&#xA;  margin: 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ul ul, ul ol {&#xA;  margin-bottom: .4em; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;caption, col, colgroup, table, tbody, td, tfoot, th, thead, tr {&#xA;  border-spacing: 0; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table {&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.25);&#xA;  border-collapse: collapse;&#xA;  display: table;&#xA;  empty-cells: hide;&#xA;  margin: -1px 0 23px;&#xA;  padding: 0;&#xA;  table-layout: fixed; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;caption {&#xA;  display: table-caption;&#xA;  font-weight: 700; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;col {&#xA;  display: table-column; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;colgroup {&#xA;  display: table-column-group; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;tbody {&#xA;  display: table-row-group; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;tfoot {&#xA;  display: table-footer-group; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;thead {&#xA;  display: table-header-group; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;td, th {&#xA;  display: table-cell; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;tr {&#xA;  display: table-row; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table th, table td {&#xA;  padding: 0 1em; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table thead {&#xA;  background: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.15);&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.15);&#xA;  border-bottom: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table tbody {&#xA;  background: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table tfoot {&#xA;  background: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.15);&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.15);&#xA;  border-top: 1px solid rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;figure {&#xA;  display: inline-block;&#xA;  position: relative;&#xA;  margin: 1em 0 2em; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;figcaption {&#xA;  font-style: italic;&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  background: white;&#xA;  color: #666666;&#xA;  position: absolute;&#xA;  left: 0;&#xA;  bottom: -24px;&#xA;  width: 98%;&#xA;  padding: 1%;&#xA;  -webkit-transition: all 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -moz-transition: all 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -o-transition: all 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  -ms-transition: all 0.2s ease-in-out;&#xA;  transition: all 0.2s ease-in-out; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;figure:hover &gt; figcaption {&#xA;  /* background: rgba(0,0,0,1) */ }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;.poetry pre {&#xA;  display: block;&#xA;  font-family: Georgia, Garamond, serif !important;&#xA;  font-style: italic;&#xA;  margin-left: 1em; }&#xA;  .poetry pre code {&#xA;    font-family: Georgia, Garamond, serif !important;&#xA;    word-break: break-all;&#xA;    word-break: break-word;&#xA;    /* Non standard for webkit */&#xA;    -webkit-hyphens: auto;&#xA;    -moz-hyphens: auto;&#xA;    hyphens: auto;&#xA;    white-space: pre-wrap; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;blockquote p {&#xA;  text-indent: 0;&#xA;  font-style: italic; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;sup, sub, a.footnote {&#xA;  font-size: 1.4ex;&#xA;  height: 0;&#xA;  line-height: 1;&#xA;  position: relative;&#xA;  vertical-align: super; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;sub {&#xA;  vertical-align: sub;&#xA;  top: -1px; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;blockquote+p {&#xA;  margin: 0; &#xA;  text-indent: 0;&#xA;  }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h2+p {&#xA;  margin: 0; &#xA;  text-indent: 0;&#xA;  }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;p, h5 {&#xA;  margin: 0; &#xA;  text-indent: 1.5em;&#xA;  }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dt, th {&#xA;  font-weight: 700; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table tr:nth-child(odd), table th:nth-child(odd), table td:nth-child(odd) {&#xA;  background: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.06); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;table tr:nth-child(even), table td:nth-child(even) {&#xA;  background: rgba(200, 200, 200, 0.25); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;@media print {&#xA;  body {&#xA;    overflow: auto; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;img, pre, blockquote, table, figure {&#xA;    page-break-inside: avoid; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;p {&#xA;    page-break-inside: auto; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;#wrapper {&#xA;    background: white;&#xA;    color: #303030;&#xA;    padding: 10px;&#xA;    position: relative;&#xA;    text-indent: 0; } }&#xA;@media screen {&#xA;  .inverted {&#xA;    background: #252a2a; }&#xA;    .inverted #wrapper {&#xA;      background: #252a2a; }&#xA;    .inverted hr {&#xA;      border-color: #333f40 !important; }&#xA;    .inverted p, .inverted td, .inverted li, .inverted h1, .inverted h2, .inverted h3, .inverted h4, .inverted h5, .inverted h6, .inverted pre, .inverted code, .inverted th, .inverted .math, .inverted caption, .inverted dt, .inverted dd {&#xA;      color: #eeeeee; }&#xA;    .inverted table {&#xA;      background: none; }&#xA;      .inverted table tr:nth-child(odd), .inverted table td:nth-child(odd) {&#xA;        background: none; }&#xA;    .inverted a {&#xA;      color: #acd1d5; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;::selection {&#xA;    background: rgba(157, 193, 200, 0.5); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h1::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(45, 156, 208, 0.3); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h2::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(90, 182, 224, 0.3); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;h3::selection, h4::selection, h5::selection, h6::selection, li::selection, ol::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(133, 201, 232, 0.3); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;code::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7);&#xA;    color: #eee; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;code span::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.7) !important;&#xA;    color: #eee !important; }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;a::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(255, 230, 102, 0.2); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;.inverted a::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(255, 230, 102, 0.6); }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;td::selection, th::selection, caption::selection {&#xA;    background-color: rgba(180, 237, 95, 0.5); } }&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2780" LastActivityDate="2017-08-14T17:55:40.660" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="7356" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7249" CreationDate="2017-08-14T19:20:07.213" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;The rights are personal to you. The consequences are more practical than legal. For example, a reader of the library copy can copy a portion of your text if such use constitutes &quot;fair use.&quot; Whether a use is permitted under the copyright law is often a close question. In general, short quotations are permitted. Copying an entire chapter is not. Failure to attribute a quote is more of an academic or journalistic crime; proffering a quote as your own is not a violation of copyright, it's plagiarism. You, as rightsholder, own the intellectual property in the text. You can sell it, or give it away (as in a CC license). For example, you could sell the copyright to your thesis and the buyer could then decide to give the thesis away. You could sell some rights (say, audiobooks) and retain others (digital editions). If you have licensed your content under Creative Commons, the existence of a printed book that predated the grant does not affect the grant or make the grant unenforceable. This answer is grounded in US law. Other countries may or may not recognize the principle of fair use. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2780" LastActivityDate="2017-08-14T19:20:07.213" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7357" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-15T15:27:36.213" Score="1" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;I left a Kindle Paperwhite with my mom a month ago and it disappeared in the house, probably in between books somewhere. I know it still connects to wifi and receives documents through the kindle email at least once a day, so it has some battery left.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there any call home, lost beep, or similar feature I could use to help focus the search?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At worst I thought of setting up some laptops/phones sniffing packages and broadcast strength coming from the kindle's mac address (it shows up every once in a while in the router logs) and triangulate that to have a gross estimation of the location. Any idea on which software would be the most appropriate for it (ideally for ubuntu/android/windows)?&#xA;Thank you for your answers before the battery runs out&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[edit]&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Found the Kindle using the sniffing technique described below. However I'd still like to know if there's a way to find it that's less overkill.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I discovered that the Kindle updates its contents daily while in deep sleep around 5:30-6:30AM. So I set up the delivery of a biggish pdf file through the kindle email so I'd ensure a long enough connection, end set up three laptops with a Kali Linux running live with airodump sniffing packages (modified from here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.androidauthority.com/capture-data-open-wi-fi-726356/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.androidauthority.com/capture-data-open-wi-fi-726356/&lt;/a&gt;  )&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following procedure can be used to physically find any active wifi device connected to a network:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Three lines of code in the terminal in at least three Kali Linux running devices (2D location, at least 4 receivers out of plane for 3D):&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To start monitor mode on a wifi card (in this case wlan0, check on iwconfig if needed):&lt;br&gt;&#xA;airmon-ng start wlan0&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Airmon usually changes the card name to wlan[n]mon after this. Check the wifi interface name on iwconfig and modify accordingly if the next line returns a related error.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Then run airodump to find your wifi network and its channel:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;airodump-ng wlan0mon&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Enter Ctrl-C to end the capture once you note the desired network's channel&#xA;Run the following line to run airodump again only at the specified channel and record the data to the &quot;allthedata.csv&quot; file in the terminal directory (usually the root for a live cd/usb if you didn't change it). Replace the square brackets by the channel number:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;airodump-ng -c [channel number 1, 6 or 11 usually] -w allthedata wlan0mon&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started the pcs before going to sleep and as I woke up a bit past the usual update time, I hit ctrl-C to stop the capture and looked up the device on the allthedata.csv files by its MAC number which can be obtained at the router logs. There are in fact 4 allthedata files with different extensions per capture, and on the xml you can find the manufacturer of the device in the logs, so even if you don't know the mac address by looking up an Amazon branded device connected to your router you may find the Kindle entry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the Kindle entry, find the signal strength value and note it for all the receiver computers.&#xA;Than convert the values from dbm to mW using the following formula: mW=10^(dBm/10)*1000.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To triangulate the signal (for a 2D location), draw a chart with the position of the laptop wifi receivers and for every pair of receivers, draw a line perpendicular to the line going through the points in a point inversely proportional to the square root of the mW power values, as the signal drops of proportionally to the square of the distance (for 3D use at least 4 receivers and a surface between the points).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lines should cross at the source of the emission - the Kindle was at a closet in this case. The margin of error was about 1m/3ft even with several concrete/brick walls in between the receivers and the emission.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[edit 2]&#xA;-This simplified location approach is only possible if the emitter is located in between the receivers, that is, a three-set of receivers (2D) form a triangle that has the emitter inside it.&#xA;-Different receivers might have different antenna gains and correcting for it will greatly increase accuracy. A quick and dirty way of doing so is positioning the receivers at the same position from a constant power emitter (wifi router, for example) and using the signal strength value difference between them as a calibration factor to be subtracted it from the signals received afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9900" LastEditorUserId="9900" LastEditDate="2017-08-20T19:45:34.990" LastActivityDate="2017-08-20T19:45:34.990" Title="Any way to find a lost Kindle inside a house?" Tags="&lt;kindle&gt;&lt;wifi&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7358" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7016" CreationDate="2017-08-16T17:05:29.033" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Alternatively you could use the free BookFusion app that allows you to read  your download books regardless of format  across IOS, Android &amp;amp; Deskptop(Web) without the additional hurdles of getting an Adobe ID&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bookfusion.com/reading&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.bookfusion.com/reading&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS: I am a founder of BookFusion. Please feel free to reach out if you have any feedback or suggestions. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9907" LastActivityDate="2017-08-16T17:05:29.033" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7359" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7351" CreationDate="2017-08-16T18:44:03.420" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;ADE is not a library, it is software to allow a person to read ebooks. Here are sources for free ebooks if that's what you want: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gutenberg.org&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.gutenberg.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://smashwords.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://smashwords.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://manybooks.net&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://manybooks.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Free classics on Amazon. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/b?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;node=2245146011&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/b?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;node=2245146011&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Baen free library, mostly scifi and fantasy. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.baen.com/catalog/category/view/s/free-library/id/2012&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.baen.com/catalog/category/view/s/free-library/id/2012&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://duckduckgo.com/?q=download+free+ebooks&amp;amp;t=hb&amp;amp;ia=web&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;DDG search for free ebooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kobo.com/us/en/p/free-ebooks&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Kobo free ebooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="6441" LastActivityDate="2017-08-16T18:44:03.420" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7360" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="920" CreationDate="2017-08-16T22:01:37.650" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can definitely create your own eBook library by combining Calibre with other solutions to ensure your books, highlights and comments are reliably accessible online which would require a lot of overhead.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a similar problem when we set out to build BookFusion. BookFusion allows you to seamlessly organize and store your eBooks and docuemtns in the cloud while accessing them on any device(Android, IOS and Web). In a gist your own personal ebook cloud library.  To learn more visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bookfusion.com/reading/cloud-library&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://www.bookfusion.com/reading/cloud-library&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS: I am a founder at BookFusion and would be happy to get your feedback. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9907" LastActivityDate="2017-08-16T22:01:37.650" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7361" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-17T23:30:34.847" Score="1" ViewCount="27" Body="&lt;p&gt;How can I publish e-books online so that I can sell them to readers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9832" LastActivityDate="2017-08-17T23:30:34.847" Title="How can I publish an ebook online?" Tags="&lt;ebook-readers&gt;&lt;pdf&gt;&lt;publishing&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="7362" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-17T23:56:32.817" Score="4" ViewCount="25" Body="&lt;p&gt;How does Amazon Kindle count a standard page?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or, if I may ask more specifically:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is a believable range of character lengths for a standard page as calculated for Amazon Kindle?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9903" LastActivityDate="2017-08-19T11:51:53.640" Title="How are Kindle standard pages calculated?" Tags="&lt;kindle&gt;&lt;amazon&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7363" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7362" CreationDate="2017-08-18T19:30:27.443" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;This can be really hard to estimate without narrowing your question down a bit. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But I just measured a text-heavy book to determine: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mobile Phone App&lt;/strong&gt; &#xA;852 characters 26 lines &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On a small e-ink device:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1217 characters ...  25 lines (3rd font size from left)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;802 characters  21 lines  (next larger size font, 2nd from left)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Large Tablet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2003 characters 41 lines somewhat small font size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1666 characters       37 lines somewhat large font size&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users can adjust text margins and text size, so that plays a role. Also, my sample didn't have many paragraphs or line breaks. I was using a custom font on my large tablet, it seems that Bookerly is slightly smaller, so maybe add an extra 100. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="417" LastActivityDate="2017-08-18T19:30:27.443" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7364" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7362" CreationDate="2017-08-19T11:51:53.640" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is a plugin for &lt;a href=&quot;https://calibre-ebook.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Calibre&lt;/a&gt; called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mobileread.com/forums/showthread.php?t=134000&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Count Pages&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It can estimate page and word counts for a given ebook, using various algorithms, and one of them is an APNX estimation based on Amazon Kindle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can try to use it and perform your own tests; if you have a decent amount of books, once it has counted the total words of each one and estimated the page numbers, you can do your math and calculate the average words per page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastActivityDate="2017-08-19T11:51:53.640" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7365" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7366" CreationDate="2017-08-20T00:36:55.070" Score="2" ViewCount="21" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there something like a small easel or book butler to be used with an ereader?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I don't like the way the device feels when I hold it.  I like holding a book, and I like hardcover books where the pages lie flat nicely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9925" LastEditorUserId="136" LastEditDate="2017-08-21T08:21:56.333" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T08:21:56.333" Title="Is there a small easel or book butler for an ereader?" Tags="&lt;ebook-readers&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="7366" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7365" CreationDate="2017-08-20T08:59:53.987" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are mini easels (like &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/B06XDHLJF9&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; from Amazon), I have seen them in all kinds of different sizes in shops catering for artists (in Germany).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Given that your ebook is rigid (all that I know are), you can easily make such a book butler by using a 20mm thick block of wood, the size of your ebook reader, and routing a slot slightly wider than your readers thickness about 2/3 deep.&#xA;If you don't have a router, you can use three 6mm pieces of wood, and from two cut off a 15mm strip and from the rest the thickness of your reader + plus a bit, then glue the 4 pieces so created on top of the full size base&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;###   #######################&#xA;###   #######################&#xA;#############################&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You put the ebook with the front to the left, and the ebook leaning like this: &lt;code&gt;/&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Make sure the &quot;groove&quot; is not to deep to cover any buttons that might be at the bottom of your reader. While it might be OK to take it out when you want to switch it off, doing so for every page turn is probably not what you want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2017-08-20T08:59:53.987" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="7367" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-20T12:41:20.697" Score="2" ViewCount="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've got comics in CBZ format with pictures in 2k or 4k pixels tall and when I try converting them to EPUB, Calibre shrinks the pictures to 1k or under, making them very blurry to view on a mobile or tablet.  Is there a setting or type of script I can use to convert each picture to its own EPUB page and not have Calibre shrink the picture?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9926" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T08:19:56.277" Title="How do I make Calibre convert CBZ to EPUB without images shrinking or conversion?" Tags="&lt;epub&gt;&lt;calibre&gt;&lt;conversion&gt;&lt;cbz&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7369" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-20T15:48:51.453" Score="0" ViewCount="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;I converted PDF t mobi using Caliber. Then opened the .mobi file in kindle previewer 3. Exported the file to desktop.&#xA;Sent the exported file to my Amazon kindle email account.&#xA;But got following reply:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;* xxxx.mobi&#xA;&#xA;The Kindle Personal Document Service can convert and deliver the following types of documents:&#xA;Microsoft Word (.doc, .docx)&#xA;Rich Text Format (.rtf)&#xA;HTML (.htm, .html) &#xA;Text (.txt) documents&#xA;Archived documents (zip , x-zip) and compressed archived documents&#xA;Mobi book&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How to get the kindle app for android to show the books cover?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9382" LastEditorUserId="60" LastEditDate="2017-08-20T16:40:55.513" LastActivityDate="2017-08-20T16:40:55.513" Title="Using Kindle Preview 3 export, Amazon says file type not supported" Tags="&lt;kindle&gt;&lt;calibre&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7370" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-20T17:10:27.233" Score="1" ViewCount="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;I was given a Kobo as a gift.  I like the idea of reading a book on an electronic device because I'd like to be able to click and see a definition of a word that I'm not familiar with, rather than going to look for the dictionary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, I'm unhappy with the width of the device.  Unless I make the font very small, every line is getting wrapped/carried to the next line.  Example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/D5W8a.png&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/D5W8a.png&quot; alt=&quot;line wrapping&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suppose I either need a format of book that will allow for fluid display of the text, or I need a larger device.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like to read pdfs as well as books.  I don't like two-column pdfs, where I have to page-down to follow the whole left-hand column, and then jump up to the right-hand column.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9925" LastEditorUserId="136" LastEditDate="2017-08-24T16:06:45.250" LastActivityDate="2017-08-24T16:06:45.250" Title="Alternative to Kobo to solve line wrapping problem" Tags="&lt;ebook-readers&gt;&lt;pdf&gt;&lt;kobo&gt;&lt;formatting&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7371" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7367" CreationDate="2017-08-20T19:57:34.980" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Try &lt;a href=&quot;https://kcc.iosphe.re/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Kindle Comic Converter&lt;/a&gt;.  Despite its name, it works for all types of readers, and can output EPUB.  Be sure to select the generic reader output, enable Color Mode, and select EPUB as the output format.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9931" LastActivityDate="2017-08-20T19:57:34.980" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7372" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7367" CreationDate="2017-08-21T08:19:56.277" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;When you open the conversion window, before actually starting the process, go to the &lt;code&gt;comic input&lt;/code&gt; tab, you will find a box labeled &lt;code&gt;change images dimensions&lt;/code&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, Calibre uses the settings from the &lt;code&gt;page setup&lt;/code&gt; tab to select standard output settings for the selected device, this includes that device screen size, to which the images are resized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By putting a custom value (in your case, the original dimensions of the pictures inside the CBZ files) on the &lt;code&gt;change images dimensions&lt;/code&gt; box, you can force Calibre to use these values instead of the preset ones from the &#xA;&lt;code&gt;page setup&lt;/code&gt; tab.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;1 - Or something similar: I'm using the italian version, the actual wording may be a little different.&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T08:19:56.277" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7373" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7370" CreationDate="2017-08-21T08:41:18.680" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I also own a Kobo ereader.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From what I can see, the rather messy output that you get is probably caused by a badly formatted ebook file, being it &lt;code&gt;.pdf&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;.epub&lt;/code&gt;. It is just a supposition, but I really think that this layout is not your ereader fault. If this is really the case, there is not much you can do about it, other than trying to find a better version of the file. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can do a quick test by downloading a properly formatted ebook file (i.e. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mobileread.com/forums/showthread.php?t=185692&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;this freely available version of Dracula&lt;/a&gt;) and seeing if you keep having this problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ereaders are mainly intended to be used with reflowable text ebook formats, like &lt;code&gt;.azw&lt;/code&gt; for Amazon Kindle and &lt;code&gt;.epub&lt;/code&gt; for the rest of the world; when acquired from legitimate sources, they are usually properly formatted.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Even if ereaders support the &lt;code&gt;.pdf&lt;/code&gt; format, it is mainly for the sake of completeness, it is a format mainly used for fixed layout pages and is not really suited to be read from a small screen; whenever you can you should rely on the above-mentioned formats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T08:41:18.680" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7374" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5940" CreationDate="2017-08-21T11:23:54.117" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt; (today's environment)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yes, you can annotate (pdf and azw...)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yes, on formats like azw.. (you can convert via amazon upload &quot;convert&quot; as email subject; or calibre) you can extract your annotations via clippings.txt on kindle paperwhite, or by sharing it around your devices (amazon upload) and export with android kindle app.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No, using pdf, getting the annotations outside seems to be difficult, you can annotate though, but for me without being able to extract them, this is a bit sensless (there are also no normal pdf annotations, like you know from adobe reader). As PDFs are the onle way for some documents (magzines, math formulars?) this is annoying. Any solution is appreciated! &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For Amazon bought books just use: read.amazon.com/kp/notebook (or the azw... possibility explained above)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I'm highly interested in reading PDFs on my kindle paperwhite 3 (the recent one), as I want a perfect reading experience (eInk/no bright display and high resolution) and the kindle paperwhite gives me that. I experimented with my kindle fire and my paperwhite, so far my insights for the kindle paperwhite are (they correspond to todays possibilities, when something changes, feel free to comment):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You &lt;strong&gt;can annotate converted ebooks and pdfs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The problem is &lt;strong&gt;how to get the annotations outsite of the kindle paperwhite&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There seem to be 3 factors:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which &lt;em&gt;software version&lt;/em&gt; (kindle) do you have?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How did you transfer the data to your ebook (by &lt;em&gt;usb&lt;/em&gt; or by &lt;em&gt;amazon uploading&lt;/em&gt;)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which &lt;em&gt;format&lt;/em&gt; do you use (pdf or epub or azw...)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The software version decides how the notes are stored on the kindle. It seems to be that in earlier version notes where stored in an &quot;mbp&quot; file format, which could be read with the right software. But amazon changed that to &quot;mpb1&quot; (I don't know, if it is possible to read that). (I tested everything with today's recent kindle version 5.8.10.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The transfer type decides if your uploaded document (only the document, didn't say anything about annotations yet) is distributed to your devices. It is distributed if you upload it via amazaon (e.g. with send to kindle via email), with USB it is not. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The format decides if your annotations are synced around your devices. This obviously only works, if the document itself is synced (uploaded via amazon). So you need to upload it via amazon and use an kindle compatible book format to share your annotations (pdf won't work).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;temp TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you want to just share your document around your devices (not annoations), use amazon uploading.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you want additionaly to share the annotations also use amazon uploading but use a compatible file format (not pdf), easiest way is, writing &quot;Convert&quot; as the subject when sending the file via email uploading.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sadly&lt;/em&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;https://read.amazon.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://read.amazon.com&lt;/a&gt; and also &lt;a href=&quot;https://read.amazon.com/kp/notebook&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://read.amazon.com/kp/notebook&lt;/a&gt;? (shows your annotations in the browser) won't work with that methods (also the windows kindle application!). They just work with amazon bought books, as I see it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For me, this is very unsatisfactory as I don't just want to have the notes on the kindle reader app or on my kindle paper white, I want it to be on my pc! Reading app for pc would only be second best option, but as I said, it doesn't work like i said in the paragraph before. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I experimented further. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;paperwhite usb to pc: There are many formats, somebody may try to open these: .apnx, azw3f, azw3r, mbp1, mbs, pds, pdt. &lt;em&gt;I didn't really, would be great if somebody finds out something&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;open the clippings.txt under documents. &lt;strong&gt;There you can find the annotations of kindle books formats (azw... and so on, but not pdf)&lt;/strong&gt; (can also be synced files), &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sharing the notations via kindle itself:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The sharing options on paperwhite are shit, you can only share a single annotation at a time, and you can share it with facebook and twitter - facepalm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The sharing options with the android fire kindle app are good and much better&lt;/strong&gt;. But this only works with formats like azw..., it does not work for pdfs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pdf annotation extraction/export seems to be difficult. This is very unsatisfactory for me, as some documents (math formulars?) and magazines can only be read properly as an pdf. I appreciate any solution in this area!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9936" LastEditorUserId="9936" LastEditDate="2017-08-21T12:10:13.867" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T12:10:13.867" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7375" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7347" CreationDate="2017-08-21T22:43:44.837" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Let me introduce you to a service (with a free option) that I'm just investigating myself.  Please note that I am NOT an employee of this company, nor a reseller, nor in anyway affiliated with them.  I'm just passing along a resource I discovered that has the potential of being really, really, really valuable (though not really, really, really tested yet.  I'm working on that).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://cloudconvert.com&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://cloudconvert.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These folks convert almost anything to anything, including HTML to PDF.  It has an API if you're tring to automate, and a dashboard if you're looking for a one-off.  You do need to sign up to use the service, free or not.  With a free option, it can't hurt to give them a try and see what they can do for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9938" LastActivityDate="2017-08-21T22:43:44.837" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7376" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-22T13:58:06.710" Score="1" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;I used to do that a year or two ago and it was pretty straightforward back than (there was «Export to epub» link or something like this on the left pane of a Wikipedia page). Not any more! Currently, there are two options for export in the book creator, namely, «pdf» and «plain text» (only «pdf» for single article).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is worse I did not manage to find any clear info on why it is not there. The article at &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Tools#PDF.2C_EPub.2C_Odt_and_LaTeX&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:Tools#PDF.2C_EPub.2C_Odt_and_LaTeX&lt;/a&gt; mentions it is still possible to produce epubs and re-directs to some weird page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do I miss anything obvious or they really disabled this useful functionality for good?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9940" LastActivityDate="2017-08-23T16:56:25.150" Title="How do I export Wikipedia article collections to epub?" Tags="&lt;epub&gt;&lt;conversion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="7378" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7376" CreationDate="2017-08-23T04:47:12.037" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;This feature was removed as the result of changes of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://mwlib.readthedocs.io/en/latest/index.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;mwlib&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that was used for export to &lt;a href=&quot;https://wikitech.wikimedia.org/wiki/OCG&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;ocg&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that has better support for non-latin scripts for PDF files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the process EPUB export was disabled, probably because the &lt;code&gt;ocg&lt;/code&gt; library renders to images via LaTeX (that is a guess, I have not looked at the details).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The announcement for the change was made on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lists.wikimedia.org/pipermail/wikitech-ambassadors/2014-September/000955.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;wikitech mailing list&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;As part of this change, we will disable ZIM and EPUB export for the&#xA;  time being. If you're interested in working on ZIM or EPUB support for&#xA;  the new offline content generator, or other export formats, please let&#xA;  us know via the above channels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and it looks like it has not come back yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What that &quot;weird&quot; page does is take the source of the wikipedia page, which has the page description, and tries to render it to ePub. That should give  better results than e.g. starting with the HTML version or the rendered PDF.   I normally caution to not use such cloud based rendering services, but since the input you feed it is public anyway, you won't have to fear that the data you upload there gets stored for further use by the website owner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2017-08-23T04:47:12.037" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="7379" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-23T08:47:23.153" Score="0" ViewCount="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've found some e-readers that &lt;em&gt;support&lt;/em&gt; Linux and Android such as FBReader, but are there any that can &lt;em&gt;sync&lt;/em&gt; progress across the two? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9946" LastActivityDate="2017-08-23T08:47:23.153" Title="E-reader that syncs progress across Linux and Android?" Tags="&lt;android&gt;&lt;linux&gt;&lt;sync&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7380" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7376" CreationDate="2017-08-23T10:34:25.443" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is an extension for Firefox called &lt;a href=&quot;http://grabmybooks.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;GrabMyBooks&lt;/a&gt; that can convert any webpage to &lt;code&gt;.epub&lt;/code&gt; format.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that it was also available for Chrome, but I'm not entirely sure, maybe I'm wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastActivityDate="2017-08-23T10:34:25.443" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7381" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7376" CreationDate="2017-08-23T16:56:25.150" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;This might not address your specific question, but I suspect that what you really want is a way to read Wikipedia articles offline on your mobile device. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recommend the app  Offline Browser app and if you have a paid subscription, you can also use Evernote. There are many other similar apps, but I think Offline Browser is the best. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="417" LastActivityDate="2017-08-23T16:56:25.150" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="7383" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2017-08-24T12:17:36.923" Score="-1" ViewCount="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anyone interested for the free exchange of the ebook in question -I've got the Mobile Forensics, I need the Criminal Behavior. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="9950" LastActivityDate="2017-08-24T12:17:36.923" Title="Exchange Mobile Forensics-Advanced Investigative Strategies for Criminal Behavior: A Psychosocial Approach" Tags="&lt;ebook-readers&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="0" />
</posts>
